

Minneapolis, MN

gallagher.reese@gmail.com  $\boxtimes$ 

spacegoats.github.io/ReeseGallagher

+1 940 536 3454

#### **BIOGRAPHY**

My name is Reese and I am a Javascript / Front End Developer with experience in programming, web design, technical support and customer service for 4+ years. I've worked for 2 years in a client facing web development role utilizing Javascript, HTML, CSS and various other tools to create beautiful and responsive client facing websites.

While I love building things from scratch, I'm also a serious tinkerer and love getting my hands dirty with new technology and really anything that rounds me out more as a person.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# From September 2016

### **Incident Manager**

Best Buy, Minneapolis, MN

Manage the process to restore normal service operation as quickly as possible to minimize the impact to business operations. Acts as the primary pivot and moderator of conference calls between technical teams with the goal of resolving an issue as well as continuous documentation of issue to better shape the incident process going forward.

#### From April 2016 to July 2016

#### Web Developer, Contractor

Rowen Advisory Partners, TX

Wrote and helped design websites using Javascript, HTML, CSS and various other Javascript frameworks as well as handles general requests from clients for updates, changes or new features on a website. Began learning full stack web development techniques using AngularJS and mySQL as well.

#### From July 2015 to April 2016

## Front End Web Developer

Third Corner LLC., Plano, TX

Wrote and helped design multiple websites from scratch using Javascript, HTML, CSS and other Javascript frameworks. Also handled almost all general website support requests ranging from Javscript bug fixing to regular HTML content updates.

### From February 2013 to October 2015

## Independent Web Designer / Creator

University of North Texas, Denton, TX

## From February 2012 to October 2014

## **Student Technician & Helpdesk**

University of North Texas, Denton, TX

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

## **Technical Skills**

HTML CSS **Javascript** Python Bootstrap jQuery AngularJS

Node SQL Git

0

Photoshop Indesign Illustrator

## Other Skills

Sketch PSD to HTML Typography Wireframes Wordpress UI/UX Design Grid & Layout Interaction Design CSS Animations Client Communication

## **EDUCATION**

From July 2012 to April 2015 0

# **Computer Science**

University of North Texas, Denton, TX, USA

#### **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**









Music

Movies

Football (Soccer)